- Then what's yourjob?
- Letting him make me happy.
(Bernadette:)I just think, in relationships,
you get back what you put in.
(Amy:)That's not always true.
(Amy:)Last night I gave Sheldon
my best come-hither look...
(Amy:)...and he responded by explaining
how wheat came to be cultivated.
(Penny:)I guess I could probably try a little harder.
(Bernadette:)You could start
by taking an interest in his work.
(Penny:)- That's kind of a problem.
- Why?
(Penny:)Not really clear on what he does.
(Bernadette:)He's an experimental physicist.
(Penny:)Yeah, I'm not really clear
on what that means.
(Amy:)He takes hypotheses and designs protocols
to determine their accuracy.
(Penny:)Yeah, you're really just making it worse.
(Sheldon:)What kind of tea would you like?
I think I'm going to try
green tea mixed with lemon zinger.
(Sheldon:)Two tea bags in one cup?
(Sheldon:)You're not at a rave.